var Data = [
    {
        "question": "",
        "op1": "",
        "op2": "",
        "op3": "",
        "op4": "",
        "answer": ""
    },
    {
        "question": "1)What is the role played by Robert Jr in Avengers?",
        "op1": "Hulk",
        "op2": "Iron Man",
        "op3": "X-Men",
        "op4": "Captain Marvel",
        "answer": "Iron Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "2)Who is the Leader of S.H.E.I.L.D?",
        "op1": "Tony Shark",
        "op2": "Natasha",
        "op3": "Maria Hill",
        "op4": "Nick Fury",
        "answer": "Nick Fury"
    },
    {
        "question": "3)In Avengers: Infinity War, what is the name of the villain who's on a mission to collect the infinity stones?",
        "op1": "Loki",
        "op2": "Ultron",
        "op3": "Thanos",
        "op4": "Red Skull",
        "answer": "Thanos"
    },
    {
        "question": "4)What is the name of Tony Stark's A.I. assistant, who becomes the basis of The Vision?",
        "op1": "H.O.M.E.R",
        "op2": "S.H.I.E.L.D",
        "op3": "J.A.R.V.I.S",
        "op4": "A.L.F.R.E.D",
        "answer": "J.A.R.V.I.S"
    },
    {
        "question": "5)Who is Gamora's sister?",
        "op1": "Aurora",
        "op2": "Meteor",
        "op3": "Nebula",
        "op4": "Asteroid",
        "answer": "Nebula"
    },
    {
        "question": "6)If Scott Lang is Ant-Man, who's the Wasp?",
        "op1": "MJ Jones",
        "op2": "Hope van Dyne",
        "op3": "Wendy Lawson",
        "op4": "Carol Danver",
        "answer": "Hope van Dyne"
    },
    {
        "question": "7)What is Peter Quill’s alter ego?",
        "op1": "Star-Man",
        "op2": "Star-Lord",
        "op3": "Star-Dude",
        "op4": "Star-Killer",
        "answer": "Star-Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "8)What Nazi organization infiltrated SHIELD?",
        "op1": "HYDRA",
        "op2": "EMPUSA",
        "op3": "CHIMERA",
        "op4": "SPHINX",
        "answer": "HYDRA"
    },
    {
        "question": "9)Where did Scott Lang work before becoming Ant-Man?",
        "op1": "Jamba Juice",
        "op2": "McDonald's",
        "op3": "KFC",
        "op4": "Baskin Robbins",
        "answer": "Baskin Robbins"
    },
    {
        "question": "10)Who is the main villain in Spider-Man: Homecoming?",
        "op1": "Mysterio",
        "op2": "Vulture",
        "op3": "Venom",
        "op4": "Kraven",
        "answer": "Mysterio"
    }
]
